<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Craymate`s Datafield</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Craymate`s Datafield</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Survey of Overall Election Employed by the Conservative Party</title>
      <link>/2020/10/02/survey-of-overall-election-employed-by-the-conservative-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/10/02/survey-of-overall-election-employed-by-the-conservative-party/</guid>
      <description>Executive SummaryNearly all political action committees, city council members, political consultants, school board districts, government agencies, rely on offline or online surveys to get the insights they need to drive their causes and run quick polls on hot-button issues.
The importance of investigation is self-evident, and a good polling update of investigation must not only reflect the reality, but also help political parties adjust the focus of their campaign activities and achieve more election goals within a limited budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 on Diferent Aspects from Toronto Cases</title>
      <link>/2020/09/26/covid-19-on-diferent-aspects-from-toronto-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/26/covid-19-on-diferent-aspects-from-toronto-cases/</guid>
      <description>AbstractIn this paper I will explore the data of COVID-19 cases from Toronto, and analyzing it in different aspects such as gender groups, age groups, fatal and resolved cases. Also, I will develop a model to pursue deeper influences from the variables and to know the level of influences by each variable. In the end, I found that age has the major influences on the outcomes ,and close contact is the major known source of infections.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
